♪
[swords clanging]
[grunts]
[growls]
[Esil gasps]
[ESIL] I surrender to you!
Please spare my life!
[SUNG JINWOO]
That voice.
Are you...
[metal clanging]
[sighs]
I am so sorry!
You won fair and square!
Now, will you let me go?
Please?
[fire crackling]
[SUNG JINWOO]
You attacked us first.
Now, you're begging for mercy?
After I killed all your men?
[ESIL] A knight's solemn duty
is to protect their master.
As long as I live
to see another day,
they would be happy, I'm sure.
[chuckles]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Happy they died?
Whatever.
♪
[ESIL]
Now's my chance!
[groans]
♪
Whatcha doing?
That was a mistake
I deeply regret,
so please don't kill me!
I'll give you
anything you want!
[SUNG JINWOO]
Unbelievable.
What about the entry permit?
Can you get me that?
[ESIL]
Yes, I certainly could!
My family is holding on
to the one for this floor,
please consider it yours
as a token for sparing my life!
And not only that, I also know
where the upper floor
permits are.
If you guarantee my
and my family's safety,
I would be happy
to serve as your guide
and show you the way.
[SUNG JINWOO] Your family's
hiding the permit.
[sighs]
Now I get it.
No wonder I couldn't find it.
One question.
[gasps]
You're a demon.
Can I trust anything
coming out of your mouth?
[ESIL]
O-of course, you can.
I speak the truth,
I'd never lie to you.
[gulps]
All right, then, you agree
to give me the permit,
I'll agree to leave in peace.
[ESIL]
Uh!
I will not soon
forget this kindness!
[fire crackling]
[SUNG JINWOO]
But would you mind...
explaining just what you are?
[wind howling]
[gnawing]
[trembling]
[screams]
[fluttering]
[ESIL] I am the eldest daughter
of the Radiru family, Esil.
[SUNG JINWOO] Cool, but not
exactly what I meant.
Huh?
[SUNG JINWOO] I was hoping
she'd give me more information
about the system,
like what I learned from Barca.
[inhales]
Do you demons hear
a voice in your heads?
Commanding you to slaughter
every human you see?
[ESIL]
Oh, umm.
Well, there is a voice,
but it gives a different order.
[SUNG JINWOO]
Which is?
To protect this place
no matter what.
When did it start?
We've heard it
since our arrival.
[SUNG JINWOO]
They came from somewhere else!
Where were you before?
[ESIL]
The demon realm.
Then one day, we woke up
and found ourselves here.
[SUNG JINWOO]
This demon realm...
what did you do there?
[crackling]
[gasps]
[ESIL] [static]
War.
We were preparing
for an imminent war.
[SUNG JINWOO]
A war?
Against who?
An adversary so strong
all demonkind
had to unite to face it.
It seemed a monumental war
was on the horizon, when...
[crackling]
[gasps]
Permitted amount
of information exceeded.
Ending conversation.
Permitted amount
of information exceeded.
Ending conversation.
Permitted amount...
[sighs]
♪
[SUNG JINWOO] I guess
that's all I'm gonna get.
[WOO JINCHUL]
This is the damage assessment
and combat log from
the winged ant appearance
on the nearby island
within Japan's borders.
It isn't pretty.
Two hundred ninety-four
civilians were killed
by the ant,
and one hundred eight
hunters deployed,
to contain it.
As for hunter casualties,
there were four E-ranks,
a single C-rank, and a B-rank.
You'd think it was
a colony's work, not one ant.
[WOO JINCHUL] The decisive
factor was an A-rank
who arrived on the scene later
and landed the fatal blow.
So, one of these
mutated ants is on par
with an A-rank hunter, then.
Hm.
That lines up
with the conclusions
from the Surveillance
Team's necropsy,
so I'd say yes.
[sighs]
[GO GUNHEE]
The attack took place
120 kilometers
from Jeju Island.
Should the ants gain any
further mastery over flight,
it will only be
a matter of time
before they reach the mainland.
Contact Japan
and request to join forces.
Reach out
to our neighbors, too.
Tell them to raise
the threat level ASAP.
[WOO JINCHUL]
Yes, sir.
We can't put it off any longer.
Time's already against us.
I want this crisis handled
before any more lives are lost.
[inhales]
Therefore, as chairman
of the Hunter's Association,
I hereby initiate
the fourth Jeju Island raid.
[ESIL] I don't know why I
suddenly passed out like that.
I'm sorry
for the extra trouble.
Nah, don't worry about it.
Are you feeling okay now?
Yes, I'm much better!
It's kind of you to ask,
considering...
[SUNG JINWOO]
Just being polite.
[Esil sighs]
[SUNG JINWOO] More importantly,
how much further is it?
Ah!
It's close!
Keep going straight
and you'll reach the castle.
Then the entry permit
will be yours!
♪
What the blazes have you
allowed into our home, Esil?
Are you mad?
He may appear to be one man.
But soldiers dwell
within his shadow,
hordes of them!
[SUNG JINWOO]
Huh, I'm impressed he noticed.
You have deceived her!
If this is an attempt
to take our castle,
I'll see you dead first!
Father, calm down!
I can explain!
Your daughter and I
have an agreement.
Hand over the permit
for the next floor
and nobody here
has to get hurt.
[gulps]
[BORGON]
This human must be the one
who slayed Vulcan and Metus.
I honestly don't see
how we could best someone
capable of that.
[deep breath]
♪
[SUNG JINWOO] Pleasure doing
business with you.
[BORGON] Pleasurable or not,
that "business" is finished.
Now begone
from my castle at once!
-There is one other thing.
-Ah?
I'd like to borrow
your daughter.
[gasps]
Cur!
[SUNG JINWOO] Oh, no,
no, no, no, not like that.
As a guide, I mean.
She said she knows where
to find all the entry permits
above this floor.
[breathing heavily]
And you won't let
any harm come to her?
I swear it.
[sighs]
Very well.
I will allow it.
Then, we're off.
We've got this.
Right, Esil?
Right!
[metal scraping]
[door opens]
Guildmaster Goto?
[fire crackling]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Nice.
That wraps up the 89th floor.
And for Tank and Igris,
that should mean...
rank promotion.
Now they're comparable
to an A-rank and an S-rank.
Which rounds out
my forces pretty well.
[glass clattering]
[sighs]
I was hoping this load
would get lighter as we went,
but I haven't had to barter
for our safe passage once.
[SUNG JINWOO] Wouldn't you
rather keep the treasure?
I brought them to trade!
Elite nobles are stewards of
the 90th floor and above,
and they're strong.
Stronger than anything you've
faced up to this point, by far.
But through negotiation,
we shall secure the permits the
same way you did with my--
Esil, if I'd been weaker
than your family's forces,
would you have agreed
to our deal?
[gasps]
[SUNG JINWOO]
That's what I thought.
You nobles are always
trying to climb
the hierarchy ladder,
aren't you?
I'm about to put your family
right at the top.
The Radi, uh, whatever family.
It's Radiru.
But...Sir Jinwoo?
You weren't obligated
to spare my family.
What made you do it?
Guess it's because I like you.
[ESIL] [trembling]
"Like?"
[SUNG JINWOO]
First Jinho, now her.
Maybe I just get along
well with people
who have...
a few toys in the attic.
Oh, yeah,
you can head back now.
Huh?
Why?
[SUNG JINWOO] You said the
enemies up ahead are no joke.
And I made a promise
to your father.
If you tell me where to find
the rest of the entry permits,
I can take it from here.
Hold on!
Do you really find me
so useless?
[SUNG JINWOO] [chuckles]
It's not that.
I just thought
it'd be dangerous.
You've done great.
Thank you.
All right!
In that case,
I'm staying with you!
Until the very end!
I want to see what you
accomplish with my own eyes!
Have it your way.
Let's head out.
[chuckles]
Onward!
[SUNG JINWOO]
Esil wasn't kidding.
I saw a drastic spike
in difficulty
on the 90th floor.
Each encampment of demons,
both in strength and numbers,
were quite literally
on another level.
But I'm keeping up,
clearing the floors
one step at a time.
Almost there.
I'm getting the last
ingredient for the elixir,
whatever it takes.
[CHOI JONG-IN]
The fourth Jeju Island raid
is in the works,
and we've both been
summoned to participate.
[CHA HAE-IN]
Of course.
[CHOI JONG-IN] President Baek
from the White Tiger Guild
has also been called upon.
In fact, every S-rank
from the country
should've received
an invitation.
[CHA HAE-IN] Which
would include Hunter Sung.
[CHOI JONG-IN] In addition,
this raid will be an official
joint operation between
us and our close neighbor.
[CHA HAE-IN]
You mean Japan.
[CHOI JONG-IN]
I do.
The recent attack
by one of these evolved ants
on Japanese soil proves
they're as much
at risk as we are.
It's the right call to make.
[exhales]
I honestly don't care as long
as we kill every last one.
♪
Have they set a date yet?
[CHOI JONG-IN]
It's still under consideration,
but I doubt they'll take
too much time to decide.
As we speak, hunters
from Japan's largest guild
are flying in.
They'll be meeting with
members of the Association
to discuss strategy.
♪
[wind gusting]
[SUNG JINWOO]
So, this is the top floor.
[ESIL] Doesn't seem
like anyone's around.
-[gasps]
-Uh?
♪
[rumbling]
[crackling]
[SUNG JINWOO] That's him,
the Demon Monarch.
Baran.
♪
[growls]
[SUNG JINWOO]
That's one daunting aura.
-I can tell this won't be easy.
-[wind gusting]
[ESIL] His sheer bloodlust
is making me weak.
[SUNG JINWOO]
Even Esil is feeling it.
And that creature he's on
could be a problem too.
A wyvern.
So, he commands
more than just demons.
[rumbling]
[electricity crackling]
♪
[rumbling]
[growling]
♪
[SUNG JINWOO]
The gang's all here, huh?
If you have an idea,
now would be the time to share!
[growling]
-Sir Jinwoo!
-Yeah, I know!
♪
[SUNG JINWOO]
Come forth!
[sword slashing]
♪
[roaring]
[fire crackling]
Incredible.
He never once showed
this kind of strength
on the floors below.
But the Demon Monarch Baran,
isn't just a boss.
He's a sovereign.
And Sir Jinwoo
invaded his castle.
He should be eliminated.
Who do I side with?
Lord Baran or Sir Jinwoo?
[electricity crackling]
[growls]
[roars]
[electricity crackling]
♪
[explosion]
[electricity crackling]
[gasps]
[ground rumbling]
Ah?
♪
[trembling]
[SUNG JINWOO]
That's no ordinary lightning.
It's wide-range magic
with a stun debuff.
I can revive my soldiers,
but my mana will deplete fast
if keeps using that move.
So, before he can...
[panting]
♪
I'll clip those wings!
[sword clanking]
He saw through Stealth?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[panting]
A homing attack?
And it's gaining on me!
Tusk! Igris!
♪
[explosion]
[growls]
[thuds]
[ground rumbling]
[SUNG JINWOO] Sorry, but
looking up was tiring me out.
C'mon, Baran, you call
yourself a Monarch, right?
Fight like one.
[growls]
Pleasure to meet you all.
My name is Hanekawa
and I belong
to the Drawn Sword Guild.
This is Ryuji Goto-san,
our guild master.
I'll be interpreting
as he only speaks Japanese.
[GO GUNHEE]
The Drawn Sword Guild.
Japan's largest,
and with eleven S-ranks,
easily their strongest, too.
Also said to be the second
largest in all Asia.
Their leader...
Ryuji Goto, has an aura
that more than lives up
to his
and his guild's reputation.
First of all,
thank you for inviting us
to join this new strike team
of allied forces.
We pledge our support.
Ah.
We should be the ones
thanking you
for even agreeing to come.
We are truly grateful to you.
As the documents
that you've received state,
we've conducted
our own investigation
into the winged ants.
and it's revealed a fair bit
of useful information.
If you could all turn your
attention to the screen.
We've provided a visual
to explain two critical points
we'd like to touch on.
One is their lifespan.
The ants grow at an
accelerated rate after hatching
but only live for about a year.
In other words,
once we exterminate the queen,
the remaining ants will die off
within a year's time.
The second point is in regard
to their behavior.
From the previous three raids,
we know that the ants
are drawn to stronger enemies.
The more mana a hunter has,
the more attracted
the ants are.
As such, we'll organize
our strategy around that trait
and use it against them.
[GO GUNHEE] We've been
aware of the ants' tendencies
for a while now,
but they've described them in
quite the elaborate breakdown.
[HANEKAWA] As for the plan,
you'll of course need hunters.
[speaking in Japanese]
[HANEKAWA] Of the Drawn Sword
Guild's 11 S-ranks,
10 will be contributing,
and that does include myself.
[all gasp]
I'm sorry,
did you say 10 will help?
[BOTH] We'll act as a decoy
and draw out the ants.
That will leave
the queen ant defenseless,
then your hunters
could move in and finish her.
But, sir.
This would require you
to fight thousands of ants.
Since we're only creating
a diversion, it should be fine.
And as AI simulations
have proven,
this plan has the highest
chance of success
and the fewest deaths.
[GO GUNHEE] Ten S-rank hunters
is certainly more
than we would be able to field.
The choice is simple.
Yes, that could work.
If there's no one here opposed,
let's begin tactical planning
with that in mind.
[growling]
[sword clanking]
[roaring]
[SUNG JINWOO] I don't even have
time to down a potion.
[roars]
♪
[growls]
[Sung Jinwoo growls]
[SUNG JINWOO]
He blocked Fatal Strike?
[grunts]
♪
[gasps]
[sword clanking]
[groans]
♪
[roars]
[SUNG JINWOO]
There goes all my mana.
♪
[electricity crackling]
[thunder rumbling]
[rain splattering]
[gasps]
♪
[sword clanking]
[growls]
[sighs]
[sword clanking]
[Sung Jinwoo growls]
♪
[gasps]
[grunts]
Shit!
My daggers!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[groaning]
[SUNG JINWOO]
He's too strong!
No, no, no, no!
I can't dodge!
[metal creaking]
♪
[Esil gasps]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Now's my chance.
I'll use all of my strength,
and combine it
with Ruler's Hand!
♪
[roaring]
That's enough!
[screaming]
♪
Who the hell do you think I am?
[explosion]
♪
He did it.
[thuds]
♪
[Sung Jinwoo sighs]
[ESIL]
Are you all right?
[SUNG JINWOO]
Esil.
Head home and give
your dad this message.
From now on, the Radish family
runs this place.
Sir Jinwoo.
[sighs]
It's Radiru.
Not Radish.
♪